马上就来
I'm on my way.
我知道这是什么
I know what this is.
这就叫做盗梦
It's called extraction.
你凭什么能做到
How can you do that?
因为我就是最出色的盗梦者
Because I am the most skilled extractor.
我能窥探你的想法 找出你大脑里的所有秘密
I know how to search your mind and find your secrets.
我精通其中窍门
I know the tricks.
斋藤都知道了 他在耍我们
Saito knows. He's playing with us.
别担心 我会搞定 相信我
Doesn't matter. I can get it here. Trust me.
情报就在保险箱里
The information is in the safe.
茉儿 你来这干嘛?
Mal,what are you doing here?
我以为你会想我的
I thought you might be missing me.
不过我再也不敢相信你了
But I can't trust you anymore.
所以呢?
So what?
一看就像是亚瑟的品味
Looks like Arthur's taste.
请坐吧
Please,have a seat.
告诉我...
Tell me...
孩子们有没有想我
Do the children miss me?
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
出去透透气
Just getting some fresh air.
你坐那别动  茉儿
Stay where you are,Mal.
天 该死
God,damn it.
转过身来
Turn around.
我想知道是谁雇你们来的
I want to know the name of your employer.
杀了他只会让他醒过来
Killing him would just wake him up.
我知道 梦境已经崩溃
I know. But the dream's collapsing.
拦住他!
Stop him!
没戏了 把他叫醒
This isn't gonna work. Wake him up.
你有所保留是因为你知道我们是来干什么的
You held something back because you knew what we were up to.
雇佣我们的公司  是可不允许我们失手的
That corporation that hired us,they won't accept failure.
我们活不过两天
We won't last two days.
柯布?
Cobb?
把你知道的告诉我们!
Tell us what you know!
我一直很讨厌这里的地毯
I've always hated this carpet.
你果然名不虚传 柯布先生
You have lived up to your reputation,Mr. Cobb.
我现在依然在梦里
I'm still dreaming.
我们不是在你的梦里
We're not in your dream.
喂 你好?
Yes,hello?
外婆说你再也不会回来了
Grandma says you're never coming back.
她在摇头
She's shaking her head.
妈妈跟你在一起吗？
Is Mommy with you?
詹姆斯 我跟你说过了
James,we talked about this.
妈妈她已经不在了
Mommy's not here anymore.
好了 孩子们 说再见吧
That's enough,kids. Say bye-bye.
下不为例
Won't happen again.
这不是我的风格
It's not the way I deal with things.
好 我来给你植入一个想法
Okay,here's me planting an idea in your head.
大象
Elephants.
告诉飞行员你们要去哪儿
Tell the crew where you want to go.
嘿 柯布先生
Hey,Mr. Cobb.
让你回家意下如何 回到美国 和孩子们团圆
How would you like to go home,to America,to your children?
这太难 你做不到 没人能做到
You can't fix that. No one can.
我最大的竞争对手是个病入膏肓的老人
My main competitor is an old man in poor health.
他的儿子马上就要接管他的公司
His son will soon inherit control of the corporation.
我想要他毁掉他父亲创建的帝国
I need him to decide to break up his father's empire.
组建你的团队吧  柯布先生
Assemble your team,Mr. Cobb.
我知道你有多想回家
I know how much you wanna go home.
只要潜入得足够深
Just have to go deep enough.
你怎么知道
You don't know that.
我以前做过
I've done it before.
你来这里安全吗？
Is it safe for you to be here?
这些都是你教我的
I'm doing what you taught me.
我可没教你去当小偷
I never taught you to be a thief.
没 你教我如何操纵别人的思想
No,you taught me to navigate people's minds.
道姆 你来这想干嘛？
What are you doing here,Dom?
我找到了回家的办法
I found a way home.
但我要你帮点忙
But I need your help.
让他们自己决定
Let them decide for themselves.
他们不必亲自进入梦境
They don't actually come into the dream.
你自己设计吧
Design it yourself.
茉儿会阻止我的
Mal won't let me.
回到现实中来吧  道姆
Come back to reality,Dom.
正在苦苦等着他们的爸爸回家
they're waiting for their father to come back home.
这个就是他们的现实
That's their reality.
我要不是走投无路  我绝不会来这求你的
I would not be standing here if I knew any other way.
我需要个和我一样出色的筑梦师
I need an architect who's as good as I was.
介绍一下 柯布先生
I'd like you to meet Mr. Cobb.
幸会
Pleased to meet you.
停
Stop.
再来
Again.
停
Stop.
这才像话
That's more like it.
比如呢？
Such as?
你必须有意识地设计每一个细节
You consciously create each aspect.
但有时候 楼房像在自己设计自己
But sometimes,it feels like it's almost creating itself,
明白 好像我发现了它
Yeah,like I'm discovering it.
你创造一个 梦境
You create the world of the dream.
你是不是从不记得梦的开始？
You never really remember the beginning of a dream,do you?
好像是的
I guess,yeah.
仔细想 艾莲涅 你怎么来这的
Think about it,Ariadne. How did you get here?
你现在到底在哪儿？
Where are you right now?
我们在做梦？
We're dreaming?
你正睡在工作坊中央
You're in the middle of the workshop,sleeping.
这是你学习分享梦境的第一课 冷静点
This is your first lesson in shared dreaming. Stay calm.
要是在做梦的话 你干嘛要保护...
If it's just a dream,then why are you covering...
做梦的时候 感觉都是真实的
When you're in it,it feels real.
所以军队开发了梦境分享系统
That's why the military developed dream sharing.
士兵可以在里面相互射击
It was a training program for soldiers to shoot,
筑梦师的工作是什么？
How did architects become involved?
干嘛不再给我们五分钟？
Why don't you give us another five minutes?
五分钟？
Five minutes?
现实世界的五分钟 相当于梦境里的一小时
Five minutes in the real world gives you an hour in the dream.
试试看你在五分钟内能做设计出什么来？
Why don't you see what you can get up to in five minutes?
其他该有的也都有了
Almost everything else is here too.
记住 你是做梦者 你设计梦境
Remember,you are the dreamer. You build this world.
这也是我们偷取信息的一种办法
That's one of the ways we extract information from the subject.
重要信息就会自动存入其中
The mind automatically fills it with information it's trying to protect.
他们为什么都看着我？
Why are they all looking at me?
因为我的潜意识怀疑这不是一个真实的世界
Because my subconscious feels that someone else is creating this world.
这可是我的潜意识 我自己没法控制
It's my subconscious,I can't control it.
这座桥我见过 它是现实中的 对吗？
I know this bridge. This place is real,isn't it?
是啊 我每天上学都会经过这
Yeah,I cross it everyday to get to the college.
绝对不能根据记忆重建场景
Never recreate places from your memory,
那总会借用熟悉的东西吧？
Well,you gotta draft from stuff you know,right?
只能借用细节...
Only use details...
这和我无关 懂吗？
this has nothing to do with me,understand?
别碰她 走开
Get off of her. Back off.
别碰她！
Get off of her!
茉儿！
Mal!
把我叫醒！  把我叫醒！
Wake me up! Wake me up!
茉儿！ 茉儿！
Mal! Mal!
叫醒我！
Wake me up!
为什么我醒不过来
Why wouldn't I wake up?
看来你见过柯布夫人了
I see you met Mrs. Cobb.
不行 必须更独特些才行
No,it must be more unique than that.
只有我知道这个特制骰子的重心在哪里
Only I know the balance and the weight of this particular loaded die.
柯布的心里问题很严重 而且他还想把那些问题藏起来
Cobb has some serious problems that he's tried to bury down there.
我绝对不会允许这样的人进入我的梦境
I'm not about to just open my mind to someone like that.
她会回来的
She'll be back.
我还从没见过有人学得这么快
I've never seen anyone pick it up that quickly before.
现实已经满足不了她了
Reality is not gonna be enough for her now.
必须冒这个险
It's a necessary risk.
神偷多了去了
There's plenty of good thieves.
只是难吗？
Just difficult?
亚瑟总说这是不可能的
Arthur keeps telling me it can't be done.
这是相当精妙的技艺
That's a very subtle art.
那么 说下你要植入的想法是什么？
So what is this idea that you need to plant?
你必须从一个最根本的问题入手
All you have to do is to start with the absolute basic.
他的催眠剂配方独一无二
He formulates his own versions of the compounds.
不记得了 看他开不开枪
I don't remember. Let's see if he starts shooting.
那边！
There!
没事
Okey.
一杯咖啡
One cafe.
柯布说了你会回来
Cobb said you'd be back.
我也不想 可...
I tried not to come. But...
什么窍门？
What kind of tricks?
在梦里 你可以把建筑设计成不可能的图形
In a dream,you can cheat architecture into impossible shapes.
看见没？
See?
等着瞧 他们会翻脸不认人的
You wait,they'll turn ugly.
没人喜欢别人在自己的大脑里乱来的
No one likes to feel someone else messing around in their mind.
柯布已经不能再筑梦了吗？
Cobb can't build anymore,can he?
他说他不熟悉设计会更安全
He thinks it's safer if he doesn't know the layouts.
为什么？
Why?
他不愿意说  我想是因为茉儿吧
He won't tell me. I think it's Mal.
她已经去世了
she's dead.
你看到的只是他潜意识里的茉儿
What you just see in there is just his projection of her.
这种多层梦境太不稳定了
That many dreams within dreams is too unstable.
六个
Six.
这种工作带游客 可不行啊
There's no room for tourists on a job like this,
斋藤先生
Mr. Saito.
他们每天来这分享梦境
They come here everyday to share the dream.
看见没？ 非常稳定
You see? Very stable.
每人每天四十个小时
About 40 hours,each and every day.
他们为什么这么做？
Why do they do it?
你来说吧 柯布先生
Tell him,Mr. Cobb.
你还做梦吗? 柯布先生
Do you still dream,Mr. Cobb?
不 他们来这是为了醒过来
No,they come to be woken up.
你没事吧 柯布先生?
Are you all right,Mr. Cobb?
放心 我没事
yeah. I'm just fine.
你和这位费舍尔先生有什么过节?
What's your problem with this Mr. Fischer?
这不用你管
That's not your concern.
斋藤先生 这...
Mr. Saito,this...
这可不是一般意义上的商业间谍活动
this isn't your typical corporate espionage.
你让我植入一个想法 我希望你能理解...
You asked me for inception,I do hope you understand that...
甚至可能会彻底改变他的人生
it may come to change everything about him.
要不是我们公司 他们早就垄断全球的能源市场了
We're the last company standing between them and total energy dominance.
我们快撑不住了
We can no longer compete.
很快他们将控制半个世界的能源供给
Soon they'll control the energy supply of half the world.
然后他们将成为新兴的强权帝国
In effect,they become a new superpower.
有传言说他们之间的关系有些纠结
Rumor is their relationship is quite complicated.
能帮我接近这个人吗?
Can you get me access to this man here?
布朗宁
Browning?
老费舍尔的左膀右臂
Fischer senior's right-hand man,
应该不难 只要你有适当的引荐信
It should be possible,if you can get the right references.
他怎么样了?
How is he?
我也不想打扰他 但...
I don't wanna bother him unnecessarily,but...
罗伯特 我们恐怕得谈谈你的继承权了
Robert,we need to talk about the power of attorney.
秃鹰已经在盘旋了
The vultures are circling.
我花了不少时间 来观察了布朗宁
I've had ample opportunity to observe Browning,
伊姆斯 我很佩服
Eames,I am impressed.
你刚刚是一个人进入梦境吗?
Were you going under on your own?
没想到这里还有别人 所以...
I didn't realize anyone was here. So...
过来 给我看看
Here,let me take a look.
迷宫设计得怎么样了?
How are the mazes coming along?
为什么要这样?
Why's that so important?
以防我们中有人把自己的防御者也带进去
In case one of us brings in our projections,
我们不能让他们知道迷宫的细节
we don't want them knowing the details of the maze.
她就会破坏整个行动
She'd sabotage the whole operation.
柯布 其他人知道吗？
Cobb,did the others know?
不 不知道
No,they don't.
万一情况变糟了 你应该告诉大家
You gotta warn them if this is getting worse.
我只想要回家
I need to get home.
这是我现在唯一关心的事情
That's all I care about right now.
你为什么回不了家？
Why can't you go home?
你怎么把一个商业策略转变成情感元素？
How do you translate a business strategy into an emotion?
我们每个人都渴望和谐、精神上的宣泄
We all yearn for reconciliation,a catharsis.
我们只能见机行事
we're gonna have to work with what we find.
在第一层梦境  我们从他和父亲的紧张关系入手
On the top level,we open up his relationship with his father,
大脑的运转速度会整整提高二十倍
Brain function in the dream will be about twenty times normal.
进入梦中梦 效果会叠加
When you enter a dream within that dream,the effect is compounded.
三层梦境 也就是十小时乘以二十...
Three dreams,that's ten hour times twenty...
不好意思
I'm sorry
我数学一向不好
math's never my strong subject.
谁愿意困在梦里长达十年？
Who would wanna be stuck in a dream for ten years?
我们可以用音乐倒计时来同步所有的坠落
We can use a musical countdown to synchronize different kicks.
他没预约外科手术、牙医 什么都没有
He hasn't any surgery schedule,no dental,nothing.
他不是该动个膝盖手术吗？
Wasn't he supposed to have a knee operation?
我们至少需要十小时
We need at least ten hours.
但你得包下头等舱
But you'd have to buyout the entire cabin,
我把那家航空公司买下来了
I bought the airline.
这样比较省事
It seemed neater.
看来我们有十个小时了
It looks like we have our ten hours.
你知道怎么找到我
You know how to find me.
你知道你该怎么做
You know what you have to do.
你来这干嘛
You shouldn't be in here.
这和你一点关系都没有
it has nothing to do with you.
这是我自己的梦
These are my dreams.
这些不仅仅是梦 这些是记忆
These aren't just dreams. These are memories.
你想尽办法让她活着 你放不下她
You're trying to keep her alive.you can't let her go.
你不懂
You don't understand.
这些都是让我追悔不已的瞬间
These are moments I regret,
那是我儿子詹姆斯
It's my son,James.
他最爱挖土 好像在挖虫子
He's digging for something,maybe a worm.
那是菲利帕
That's Philippa.
不管我做什么都无法改变那一刻
Whatever I do I can't change this moment.
就在我想喊他们时 他们跑开了
When I'm about to call out to them,they run away.
我要想再见到他们 就一定得回家
If I'm ever gonna see their faces again,I've gotta get back home,
来猜个谜语吧
I'll tell you a riddle.
你在等一趟火车 它会把你带去远方
You're waiting for a train,a train that will take you far away.
但这并不重要
But it doesn't matter.
道姆 你怎么能把她带过来？
How could you bring her here,Dom?
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
这是我们庆祝结婚纪念日的套房
This is a hotel suite where we spent our anniversary.
这里发生过什么？
What happened here?
我会回来找你 我保证
I'll come back for you,I promise.
你觉得建一座记忆监狱 就能关住她吗？
Do you think you can just build a prison of memories to lock her in?
是时候了 老费舍尔刚在悉尼去世
It's time.Maurice Fischer just died in Sydney.
罗伯特必须在周二前去护送遗体
Robert should accompany the body no later than Tuesday.
但你得把我刚才看见的都告诉亚瑟
but then you have to show Arthur what I just saw.
在飞机上加个位子
Get us another seat on the plane.
谢谢
Thank you.
一样 谢谢
Same,please.
那个...谢谢
Umm... thank you.
来 敬你父亲 愿他安息
Hey,to your father. May he rest in peace.
上来
Come on.
这里有五百美元
There's five hundred dollars in there,
我们被一列火车截住了
We were blocked by a freight train.
那些人都不是普通的防御者
Those were not normal projections.
你应该把他的底细调查清楚!
You were meant to check Fischer's background thoroughly!
对这种袭击 我们完全没有防备!
We are not prepared for this type of fire!
他太痛苦了 我要把他叫醒
He's in agony. I'm waking him up.
不行 你唤不醒他的
No,it won't wake him up.
好吧 那死了会怎样?
Right. so what happens when we die?
几十年 也许是永远 我怎么知道
Decades,it could be infinite,I don't know.
问他吧 他去过
Ask him. he's the one who's been there.
我们现在 困在费舍尔的潜意识里
now we are trapped in Fischer's mind
不应该有危险的
There wasn't meant to be any risk.
这是深入三层梦境的唯一方式
This is the only way to go three layers deep.
我相信他
I trusted him.
而且他说他以前干过
Besides,he said he had done it before.
我只是竭尽所能回到我的孩子身边
I did what I had to do to get back to my children.
所以你就把我们领向一条不归路
So you led us into a war zone with no way out?
大家继续按计划行事 速战速决
We continue on with the job,and we do this as fast as possible,
拉倒吧 走得越深我们就越危险
Forget it. If we go any deeper,we just raise the stakes.
十小时的航线 在这一层就是一个礼拜
The ten hours of flight time is a week at this level.
闭嘴 没那么简单
Shut up! It won't be.
你老爸办公室的书橱下 有个保险箱
In your father's office,below the bookshelves,is his personal safe.
那不代表你不知道密码 快告诉我们
It doesn't mean you don't know the combination. Tell us what it is.
我不知道
I don't know.
彼得叔叔
Uncle Peter.
给你一小时 谈吧
You have one hour. Start talking.
你还好吧?
Are you okey?
这帮混蛋关了我整整两天
Those bastards've had me for two days.
他们派人潜入了你父亲的办公室
They have someone with access to your father's office.
他们以为我知道密码 可我不知道
They thought I'd know the combination,but I don't know it.
你是唯一知道密码的人
you are the only one to be able to open it.
只是你不知道那就是密码
maybe you just didn't know it was a combination.
我妈去世后 你知道他跟我说什么吗?
After my mother died,you know what he told me?
他不善表达情感
he was bad with emotions.
等我们到下面几层 疼痛感就会减弱
When we get down to the lower levels,the pain will be less intense.
醒来后 会完全丧失意识
When he wakes up,his mind is completely gone.
柯布 我仍会履行我们的协议
Cobb,I'll still honor the arrangement.
你醒来后 根本不会记得我们曾有过协议
When you wake up,you won't even remember that we had an arrangement.
不 我会回来 和你们一起重回年轻
No,I'll come back. and we'll be young men,together again.
深呼吸
Breathe.
他们会把我们塞进货车 把车丢进河里喂鱼
They're gonna whack us in that van and then drive it into the river.
好吧 那保险箱里到底有什么？
Alright,what is it in the safe?
是留给你的东西
Something for you.
你父亲总说 那是他留给你最珍贵的礼物
Maurice always said it was his most precious gift to you.
如果你愿意 完全可以推翻前一份
This would supersede the other,if you want it to.
他很爱你 罗伯特 以他独特的方式
He loved you,Robert,in his own way.
他临终前 把我叫到他床边
At the end,he called me to his deathbed.
你什么时候进入过迷失域？
When were you in limbo?
虽然你成功说服了大家继续执行任务
You might have the rest of the team convinced to carry on with this job,
我们在研究在梦里做梦的可能性
We were exploring the concept of a dream within a dream.
我们为自己创造了一个世界
We created and built a world for ourselves.
我们建了很多年
We did that for years.
我们建起了只属于我们自己的世界
We built our own world.
天呐 你们怎么能受得了？
Jeez. How could you stand it?
但问题是这些都不是真的
The problem was none of them was real.
你们醒来后发生了什么？
What happened when you woke up?
我知道她有点不对劲
I knew something was wrong with her.
只是她自己不愿承认
she just wouldn't admit it.
她最终告诉了我真相
Eventually,she told me the truth.
想要回去 我们俩都必须自杀
In order to get back home,we had to kill ourselves.
那你们的孩子呢？
What about your children?
你以为我看不出区别吗？
Don't you think I can't tell the difference?
如果我在做梦 为什么我会控制不了它？
If this is my dream,why can't I control this?
因为你不知道自己在做梦
Because you don't know you're dreaming!
她是如此坚决 不管我怎么解释
She was certain there was nothing I can do,
她太爱我了 所以...
She loved me too much,so...
在我们结婚纪念日那天 她想了一个办法
She came up with the plan on our anniversary.
不
No.
我们谈得够多了
we've talked enough.
茉儿
Mal.
好
Okey.
我不能跳 你知道我不会跳的
I can't. you know I can't do that.
为孩子们想想
Take a second to think about our children.
想想詹姆斯 想想菲利帕
Think about James,think about Phillipa
你在等一趟火车
you're waiting for a train,
她找了三个心理医生 证明她心智正常
She had herself declared sane by three different psychiatrists,
好吧 我们走
Alright,let's go.
我丢下了我的孩子
I left my children behind,
自那以后我就一直想办法回去
And I've been trying to buy my way back ever since.
你的罪恶感塑造了她 她才如此强大
Your guilt defines her,it's what powers her.
但你不必孤身奋战
But you don't have to do that alone.
我不知道什么密码 至少在清醒时是不知道的
I don't know any combination,not consciously anyway.
他们父子间的关系比我们想象的还糟
That boy's relationship with his father is even worse than we imagined.
该死！
Damn it!
其实这不是真的 对吧？
That's not true at all,is it?
你是说梦境吗？
Are you talking about dreams?
我是来这保护你的
I'm here to protect you.
费舍尔先生 我之所以过来保护你
Mr.Fischer,I'm here to protect you
你感觉到了吗？
You feel that?
出什么事了？
What's happening?
我们还是走吧
We should probably get out of here.
你感觉到了吗？
Do you feel that?
注意天气的反常和重力的变向
Pay attention to the strangeness of the weather,the shift of the gravity.
这一切都不是真的 你在做梦
None of this is real. You're in a dream.
你必须意识到你是在梦里 我是来保护你的
Accept the fact that you're in the dream,and I'm here to protect you.
继续想想
Go on.
我是你潜意识里的防御者
I'm a projection of your subconscious.
想要我救你 你得保持冷静
If you want my help,you have to remain calm.
费舍尔先生 你得和我合作才行
I need you to work with me,Mr. Fischer.
如果这是梦 只要自杀就能醒 对吗？
If this is a dream,I should just kill myself to wake up. Right?
费舍尔先生 换做我就不会这么做
I wouldn't do that if I were you,mr. fischer.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
这就像你醒来回想自己的梦一样难
It's like trying to remember a dream after you've woken up.
他们想从你的潜意识里偷取一串数字
They were trying to extract the number from your subconscious.
跟着他 看看他会做什么
Let's follow him and see how he behaves.
我不能让你毁掉它
I can't let you destroy it.
我要你以其人之道还治其人之身
I need you to do the same thing to him that he was going to do to you.
好吧
All right.
他睡过去了
He's out.
你没事吧？
Are you good?
伊姆斯 这是你的梦境
Eames,this is your dream.
我要你引开医院里的警卫 明白吗？
I need you to draw the security away from the complex. Do you understand?
好的 那你呢？
Alright. What about you?
行动！
Move!
快上！
Go!
但愿你们准备好了
Hope you're ready.
不不 这太早了
No,it's too soon.
柯布 听到了吗
Cobb,do you hear that?
在那！
There!
我是照迷宫设计的
It's designed as a labyrinth.
伊姆斯
Eames.
他加了一条穿过迷宫的通风系统
He added an airduct system that can cut through the maze.
好极了 告诉他们
Good,explain it to them.
如需拨打电话 请挂机后重试
If you want to make a call,please hang up and try again.
亚瑟还有几分钟 我们还有二十多分钟
Arthur has a couple of minutes,we have about twenty.
你还行吗？
Are you okey?
保险库有窗户吗？
Does the strong room have windows?
好了 我们到了
Okey. We are here.
值得一试
That's worth a shot.
我是说 茉儿也会在下面
I mean,Mal's gonna be down there.
我知道去哪找她 费舍尔肯定在她手里
I know where to find her. She'll have Fischer.
她想让我去下面找她
She wants me to come after her,
这种工作 带游客可不行
No room for tourists on this job.
这些都你们造的？ 太不可思议了
You built all this? This is incredible.
我们造了许多年
We built it for years.
跟我来
This way.
这是我们住的街区
This is our neighborhood,
那是我们的第一间公寓
That was our first apartment.
后来搬到那面去了 茉儿怀孕后
And we moved to that building right there,after Mal became pregnant,
来吧
Come on.
你准备怎么把费舍尔带回去？
How would you bring Fischer back?
我知道什么是真的 茉儿
I know what's real,Mal.
承认吧
Admit it,
你早就不再相信所谓的现实了
you don't believe in one reality anymore.
因为你抛弃了他们
Because you left them,
因为你离开了我们
because you left us.
你没搞清楚
You're confused.
我们的孩子在这里
Our children are here.
你也想再见见他们吧？
And you'd like to see their faces again,wouldn't you?
别这样 茉儿 求你了
Don't do this,Mal. Please.
我很愧疚 茉儿
I feel guilt,Mal.
什么真相？
What truth?
她在说什么？
What is she talking about?
于是我决定去寻找它
So I decided to search for it,
我闯了进去
I broke in.
你在等一趟火车
You're waiting for a train,
但这并不重要
But it doesn't matter.
因为我们会在一起！
Because we'll be together!
死亡是唯一的解脱
That death was the only escape.
你背叛了我
You betrayed me.
但你仍可以补救 继续遵守你的诺言
But you can make amends,you can still keep your promise.
我们还是能在一起
We can still be together,
柯布 我们必须找到费舍尔
Cobb,we need to get Fischer.
你们找不到他的
You can't have him.
费舍尔在门廊上
Fischer's on the porch.
快去看看他是不是还活着 快
Go check if he's alive,right now. Do it.
柯布 他在这  时间到了 你该出来了！
Cobb,he's here. And it's time. You have to come now!
帮我把费舍尔 带回去 好吗？
Take Fischer with you,alright?
看看你自己
Look at you,
你只是个幻影
you're just a shade.
你是我真正妻子的影子
You're just the shade of my real wife.
这样感觉够真实了吧？
Doesn't this feel real?
你说你梦到我们一起慢慢变老
You said you dreamt that we grow old together.
我们厮守了一生
we had our time together.
你是来杀我的吗？
Have you come to kill me?
我一直在等一个人
I'm waiting for someone,
柯布？
Cobb?
怎么可能
Impossible.
我回来找你了
I've come back for you,
这个世界不是真的
That this world is not real.
跟我回去吧
Come back with me.
先生 热毛巾要吗？
Hot towel,sir?
大概二十分钟后 我们会抵达达洛杉矶
We will be landing in Los Angeles in about twenty minutes.
入境登记表要吗？
Do you need immigration forms?
谢谢
Thank you.
欢迎回家 柯布先生
Welcome home,Mr. Cobb.
谢谢你
Thank you.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
这边
This way.
瞧瞧谁回来了
Look who's here.